export const data = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: 'What is React?',
        answer: 'A JavaScript library for building user interfaces'
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: 'What is JSX?',
        answer: 'Syntax extension to JavaScript. We recommend using it with React to describe what the UI should look like.'
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: 'Components and Props',
        answer: 'Components let you split the UI into independent, reusable pieces, and think about each piece in isolation. Conceptually, components are like JavaScript functions. They accept arbitrary inputs (called “props”) and return React elements describing what should appear on the screen.'
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: 'State',
        answer: 'The state is a built-in React object that is used to contain data or information about the component.'
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: 'What are React lifecycle methods?',
        answer: 'You can think of React lifecycle methods as the series of events that happen from the birth of a React component to its death. Every component in React goes through a lifecycle of events.'
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: 'JS Events?',
        answer: 'Events are actions or occurrences that happen in the system'
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: 'Conditional Rendering',
        answer: 'In React, you can create distinct components that encapsulate behavior you need. Then, you can render only some of them, depending on the state of your application.'
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: 'Lists and Keys',
        answer: 'A key is a unique identifier. In React, it is used to identify which items have changed, updated, or deleted from the Lists.'
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: 'Controlled Components',
        answer: 'those in which form\'s data is handled by the component\'s state'
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: 'Uncontrolled Components',
        answer: 'What are uncontrolled components in React? Uncontrolled components are those for which the form data is handled by the DOM itself'
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: 'Lifting State Up',
        answer: 'Often, several components need to reflect the same changing data. We recommend lifting the shared state up to their closest common ancestor. '
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        question: 'Composition vs Inheritance',
        answer: 'React has a powerful composition model, and we recommend using composition instead of inheritance to reuse code between components.'
    },

];